PERSONAL INFORMATION



Paweł Dabała

Nationality: Polish

+61 423 000 390

pawel.dabala@gmail.com

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/pub/paweł-dqbała/96/776/902

Skype: pawelkrzysztofdabala

GitHub: https://github.com/SuperXtra

Visa type: Work and holiday (expiration date 9th of July 2020)

Preferred contact time: Please call after 3 p.m. (UTC+10)

MOTIVATION

I am fully committed person who is constantly developing and learning to become a better professional. My focus is placed on the software development using JVM languages (Java and Scala) and currently expanding myself to become full stack using React.

I am looking for new challenges and I would be happy to have the chance to achieve this with my current skill set and several years of experience in information technology. I am looking forward to add value to your team.

I am looking for a great opportunity for growth. Attached are the references from my last employers for your convenience.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Execon ITs – Java Developer

- Developing fraud prevention system using Java 8 and Spring framework
- Continuously improving existing microservices by adding new features
- Applications developed using microservices architecture
- Dockerizing microservices
- Development made using test driven development(JUnit, Mockito, REST Assured)
- Coordinate with Analysts
- Cooperating with Testers
- Creating documentation

DELL EMC – Account Manager – Mid Market

Sales – medium accounts

Rest of responsibilities as below

DELL EMC - Account Manager - Large Commerce

- Sales Large Commerce accounts
- Consultative selling
- Virtual team management
- Relationship building
- Identifying and analysing customer needs
- Direct sales of all IT product listings
- Preparation of commercial offers

DELL EMC – Account Manager – Mid Market

- Internal sales, global corporate accounts
- Relationship business
- Relationship building
- Identifying and analysing customer needs
- Direct sales of all IT product listings
- Solving problems and consulting
- Preparation of commercial offers

Orange Polska – internship – help with service delivery – project coordinator

- Scheduling work of Orange Polska field operations and technical partner
- Equipment ordering (solutions based on Cisco)
- Provide implementation status report for OBS Order Delivery Manager & Project Manager
- Order validation with local Customer
- Feasibility study & pre-sales technical support for Business Managers

01.2019-06.2019

02.2018-12.2018

09.2017-02.2018

09.2016-09.2017

12.2015-01.2016

EDUCATION	
2016 - 2019	Warsaw University of Technology, Global Production Engineering and Management (EN)-Master of Engineering
2012 – 2016	Warsaw University of Technology, Management and Production Engineering (PL)-Bachelors of Engineering
2013 – 2014	Universidad Europea de Madrid, Madrid, Spain – European exchange program LLP Erasmus
COURSES	Java BootCamp on-line – Code Academy Object-oriented programming – scripts creation in Java
03.2018 - 07.2018	 Creating applications using Spring framework Database design (SQL). Implementation of database using DAO. Creating responsive websites (HTTP, XML, JSON, HTML)
SKILLS	
Technical	 Server side technologies: Java 8, Scala, Spring boot, Play Client technologies: CSS, HTML, Bootstrap, Angular 6 (basics), React Databases and ORM's: Postgres, NoSQL (Cassandra and Mongo), JDBC, Hibernate, JPA Servers: Apache Tomcat Version control systems: GIT Issue tracking: JIRA Virtualization: Docker Testing: Junit, Mockito, Karate, Postman Other: Swagger, JBoss – JBPM
Languages	 Polish – native language English – C1 – Confirmed by Cambridge Certificate in Advanced English and TOEFL iBT® Spanish – B1
Communication	 Communication skills gained through an internship in Spain – working with people from all over the world on university projects Experience in team working to secure cultural differences in multi country environment
Organisational	 Leadership skills – leading and managing project consisted of 40 people Distributed team management developed through university activities Teamwork achieved by playing football in a team
ADDITIONAL	• Open-minded
Other skills	 Well organized Time management Flexibility Hard-working Driving license
Hobbies	GymFootballPsychology



Dell Sp. z o.o. ul. Inflancka 4A 00-189 Warszawa Poland Tel: (48-22) 579 59 99 Fax: (48-22) 579 59 98 www.dell.com.pl

To Whom It May Concern,

REFERENCES

Mr. Paweł Dąbała has been hired in 2016 at Graduate Program in Dell Poland. Thanks to his selling skills and engagement we decided to hire him on standard position. He worked as Internal Sales Representative in Mid-Market Segment till end of 2018.

He was responsible for developing selling Dell products and services to Global and Medium companies, including proposing new solutions and new lob extension. He worked in an international team and had really good relationships with all team members. I was his direct manager and my opinion is that Pawel is very quick learner, precise and detail-oriented. He has learnt our corporate procedures and tools from basic to good level for less than one year. He had couple of occasions to participate in some trainings for our team about newly introduced or existing functionalities and he did his best. Always was open for knowledge and best practices sharing. Moreover, he is also very driven and passionate about his duties, that made me a pleasure to work with him.I would really recommend Paweł to all position connected with technology and not only.

Yours faithfully,

Magdalena Stańska-Żaczek

Magdalena stanska-za@dell.com
+48 501 695 293

Sales Manger Mid Market

Dell Technologies

ul. Inflancka 4A 00-189 Warszawa To Whom It May Concern,

I have been cooperating with Pawel Dabala since January 2019 at Execon ITS. During this time I have been leading him as a manager and I involved Pawel as Java Developer in numerous assignments.

Pawel has been a member of my project team developing digital services for the telecommunications provider. During the time we have been working together, Pawel was responsible for various development tasks through full SDLC. He proved that he is accountable and can deliver assigned tasks with the complete process understanding.

Pawel is a person who always shows full commitment and thoroughly carries out all his assignments. He is able to work as part of a team as well as he takes initiative when necessary. On top of his in-depth knowledge of many demanding technologies he is also able to build strong relationships with clients.

Pawel is very competent in software development and I strongly recommend him as an employee.

Kind regards,

Piotr Grabowski

e: piotr.grabowski@execon.pl

m: +48 600 103 208

Man P.